{"data":[{"question":"More than one person ___ interested in the problem.","a":"were","b":"was","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The expression \"more than one\" (oddly enough) takes a singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the rest of the audience refuse to go out?","a":"Does","b":"Have","c":"Has","d":"Do","answer":"4","explain":"\n- \"Of phrase \" some of, all of, none of, the rest of...): look at the noun after the preposition to determine whether to use a singular or plural verb. If the object of the preposition is singular, use a singular verb. If the object of the preposition is plural, use a plural verb \n- Audience always uses with plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"What annoys me about them ___ their constant complaints.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"has","d":"have","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Do not be misled by a phrase that comes between the subject and the verb. The verb agrees with the subject, not with a noun or pronoun in the phrase \n- The subject is \" What annoys me\"- singular","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither the Giants nor the Tigers ___ to win the pennant.","a":"have gone","b":"has gone","c":"is going","d":"are going","answer":"3","explain":"\n- When two or more singular nouns or pronouns are connected by or or nor, use a singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"A number of people ___ for a train at the station.","a":"is waiting","b":"are waiting","c":"have been waited","d":"has waiting","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The expression the number is followed by a singular verb while the expression a number is followed by a plural verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Mathematics ___ a very difficult subject for me.","a":"have","b":"has","c":"are","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Mathematics is uncountable noun - uses with singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"It is mosquitoes which ___ malaria.","a":"has caused","b":"causes","c":"cause","d":"is causing","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The pronoun who, that, or which is the subject of a verb in the middle of the sentence. The pronouns who, that, and which become singular or plural according to the noun directly in front of them","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Eighty dollars _________ a small sum for my pocket money.","a":"has","b":"have","c":"are","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The word dollars is a special case. When talking about an amount of money, it requires a singular verb, but when referring to the dollars themselves, a plural verb is required","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Every boy and every girl ___ to church every Sunday.","a":"goes","b":"go","c":"are going","d":"have gone","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Every boy - singular; Every girl - singular. So, every boy and every girl doesn't go together - one by one at the different time - singular verb (not a boy and a girl) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Romeo and Juliet ___ one of my favorite plays.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"have been","d":"were","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Romeo and Juliet is the name of a play - Singular verb","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"65","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}